<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Inspiring People</string>
    <string name="firstman">Alan Turing\n23.6.1912. - 7.6.1954.\nAlan Mathison Turing was an English computer scientist, mathematician, logician, cryptanalyst and theoretical biologist. He was highly influential in the development of theoretical computer science, providing a formalisation of the concepts of algorithm and computation with the Turing machine, which can be considered a model of a general purpose computer. Turing is widely considered to be the father of theoretical computer science and artificial intelligence</string>
    <string name="secondman">John von Neumann\n28.3.1903. - 8.2.1957.\nJohn von Neumann was a Hungarian-American mathematician, physicist, inventor, computer scientist, and polymath. He was a pioneer of the application of operator theory to quantum mechanics, in the development of functional analysis, and a key figure in the development of game theory and the concepts of cellular automata, the universal constructor and the digital computer. He published over 150 papers in his life: about 60 in pure mathematics, 20 in physics, and 60 in applied mathematics, the remainder being on special mathematical subjects or non-mathematical ones. His last work, an unfinished manuscript written while in the hospital, was later published in book form as The Computer and the Brain.</string>
    <string name="thirdman">Dennis Ritchie\n9.9.1941. - 12.10.2011.\nDennis MacAlistair Ritchie was an American computer scientist. He created the C programming language and, with long-time colleague Ken Thompson, the Unix operating system. Ritchie and Thompson received the Turing Award from the ACM in 1983, the Hamming Medal from the IEEE in 1990 and the National Medal of Technology from President Bill Clinton in 1999. Ritchie was the head of Lucent Technologies System Software Research Department when he retired in 2007. He was the "R" in K&amp;R C, and commonly known by his username dmr.</string>
    <string name="firstman_quote">“Sometimes it is the people no one can imagine anything of who do the things no one can imagine.” </string>
    <string name="secondman_quote">“Computers are like humans - they do everything except think.”</string>
    <string name="thirdman_quote">“When I read commentary about suggestions for where C should go, I often think back and give thanks that it wasn\'t developed under the advice of a worldwide crowd.” </string>
</resources>
